<resources>
    <string name="app_name">BPD App</string>
    <string name="titleTripuraPolice">"Tripura Police "</string>
    <string name="log_out">Log Out</string>
    <string name="log_out_confirmation">Are you sure you want to log out?</string>
    <string name="cancel">cancel</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="search_manually">Search manually</string>
    <string name="about_tripura_police2">Tripura Police works with zeal to maintain the law and order in the state, protecting the rights of the people and ensuring a congenial and secure society for them to live in. The Tripura Police is often applauded across the Indian Nation for its modest approach towards a common man. It is regarded to be one of the most disciplined state police forces in India. Tripura Police has contributed a lot towards fighting insurgency in the state of Tripura. The police of Tripura maintain the amiable and friendly nature that makes them more approachable by the citizens.</string>
    <string name="about_tripura_police">Tripura Police works with zeal to maintain the law and order in the state, protecting the rights of the people and ensuring a congenial and secure society for them to live in. The Tripura Police is often applauded across the Indian Nation for its modest approach towards a common man. It is regarded to be one of the most disciplined state police forces in India. Tripura Police has contributed a lot towards fighting insurgency in the state of Tripura. The police of Tripura maintain the amiable and friendly nature that makes them more approachable by the citizens. The continuous service provided by the police in the state has ensured a safe and secure heaven in the north eastern border state of Tripura. The Tripura Police headquarters is located at Agartala, the capital of Tripura state. Entire Tripura Police is divided into two ranges, The Southern Range consisting of West, Sepahijala, South, Khowai, Gomati districts and the Northern range consisting of North, Dhalai. Unakoti districts. It had in all 77 police stations across the state. Serving under Tripura police is a real challenging job for reasons like:-\nPHQ Circulars\nArchives\n⚫ The state is having 80% (Approx) of its area with International border i.e Bangladesh from three sides. • Insurgency problems are still continuing in few pockets.\n⚫ 19 tribes, Bengalis and other minority community people are living together.\nHilly terrain covering approx 80% of the land mass.\nHigh Literacy rate generating consciousness about rights and legalities.\nWe are approximately 28.031 strong police force of the state of Tripura in Republic of India including Women Police, supported by a sanctioned strength of 3,036 Home Guards Volunteers, 4,011 Special Police Officers (SPO) and 989 Ministerial Staffs. We serve a population of over 31 Lakhs residing in this state spread over an area of 10,491 square kilometers.</string>
</resources>